//問題文を格納する要素です
const quiz = [
    {
      question: "The Seven Tactics for Attracting Customer is _____ reading for students who major in marketing.",
      answers: ["required", "requires", "requiring", "require"],
      correct: "required"
    },
    {
      question: "The president continued to be an influential public figure, _____ his term in office had come to an end.",
      answers: ["during", "even as", "in spite of", "consequently"],
      correct: "even as"
    },
    {
      question: "The official has _____ Mr.Vandenberg that he will be assigned a certain amount of work within five days.",
      answers: ["expected", "transferred" ,"requested", "assured"],
      correct: "assured"
    },
    {
      question: "A completed application form should be presented to the security office in order to purchase a parking _____.",
      answers: ["permit", "permitted", "permission", "to permit"],
      correct: "permit"
    },
    {
      question: "_____ is interesting about the novel is how the lives of the characters, who are initially strangers, become interwined.",
      answers: ["That", "It", "What", "Which"],
      correct: "What"
    },
    {
      question: "For more information on available job positions and _____ an online application, please visit the company Web site.",
      answers: ["to complete", "completes", "completing", "completion"],
      correct: "to complete"
    },
    {
      question: "The new guidelines regarding jury duty should be _____ to strictly.",
      answers: ["respected", "adhered", "willing", "set"],
      correct: "adhered"
    },
    {
      question: "_____ the trains are running on schedule, Mr.Banks will arrive in Newburg City by 4 P.M.",
      answers: ["Upon", "Accordingly", "Because of", "Provided that"],
      correct: "Provided that"
    },
    {
      question: "The memo asks all employees _____ conference rooms to get approval from their departmental supervisors.",
      answers: ["reservation", "reserving", "have reserved", "reserved"],
      correct: "reserving"
    },
    {
      question: "With fuel prices at record highs, visitors to auto dealerships were not even looking at SUVs, _____ buying them.",
      answers: ["much less", "less than", "more or less", "at least"],
      correct: "much less"
    },
    {
      question: "The president's passionate speech, currently posted at www.nationalpolitico.com, _____ was written by one of his daughters.",
      answers: ["reports", "reporter", "reported", "reportedly"],
      correct: "reportedly"
    },
    {
      question: "Before expressing his frank opinions, Mr.Hashimoto told the committee members to _____ his rudeness.",
      answers: ["pardon", "ask", "recover", "hold"],
      correct: "pardon"
    },
    {
      question: "The firm hired an outside consultant to help _____ plans for expansion throughout the next decade.",
      answers: ["implements", "implementing", "implement", "implementer"],
      correct: "implement"
    },
    {
      question: "_____ portable music players of the past used media such as cassette tapes and CDs, modern devices store music on memory chips.",
      answers: ["Among", "Whereas", "Still", "Otherwise"],
      correct: ""
    },
    {
      question: "As _____ in the meeting yesterday, three samples will be sent to your factory next week.",
      answers: ["discussing", "discusses", "discussion", "discussed"],
      correct: "discussed"
    }
  ];